The prerequisites for this Nanodegree program,
这个 Nanodegren 计划的必备条件
are that you should be an intermediate level software programmer in any language.
您应该是任何语言的中级软件程序员
As long as you know concepts like variables, conditionals,
只要你知道变量 条件
loops, and functions, you're ready to learn C++.
循环 功能 您已准备好学习 C++
We also expect that you know how to execute programs ideally from the terminal,
我们还期望您知道如何理想地从终端执行程序
and that you're familiar with software debugging.
你熟悉软件调试
It will be helpful if you're familiar with concepts
熟悉概念会有帮助的
like classes in object-oriented programming,
比如面向对象程序设计中的类
but that's not required.
但这不是必需的
If you feel like you need to learn a little bit more about
如果你觉得需要多了解一点
software programming before proceeding on with this Nanodegree,
软件编程 然后再继续此 Nanodegres
then I suggest either Udacity's intro to programming Nanodegree program,
那我建议要么 Udacity 简介 Nanodegres 节目
or our intro to self-driving cars Nanodegree program.
或者我们的自驾汽车 Nanodegres 计划
Our intro to programming Nanodegree program
我们的 intro 编程 Nanodegres 程序
will teach you the basics of software engineering,
会教你软件工程的基础知识
and our intro to self-driving cars Nanodegree program
还有我们的自驾汽车 Nanodegren 计划
will teach you the basics of software engineering,
会教你软件工程的基础知识
C++ specifically, along with topics like machine learning, physics, and mathematics.
特别是 C++  还有机器学习 物理和数学